and when it comes to what this shoots best and what we do with copilot and when
we use copilot well copilot looks exactly and works exactly like all the other
chatbots that we've gone through right but the point of our copilot again is
that it is a branch and a product of Microsoft and this makes it so compatible
with other Microsoft tools as well so if you're a Microsoft user if your if you
use Microsoft products on a daily basis and if you use them a lot and there's a
lot of them you know if I go through the list of them so as you see we have
plenty of softwares done by Microsoft so when it comes to educational let's
say yeah these are operating systems productivity for example we have Microsoft
Office you know and there are a lot of useful products Excel for example is a
product of Microsoft Word is a product of Microsoft PowerPoint is a product
of Microsoft you know or Outlook the email system you know or a lot of them
you know a lot of them and these all again make another ecosystem just like
what we have with Google these make an ecosystem of Microsoft products and we
have a Microsoft ecosystem over here and this ecosystem again suits best
with the AI chatbot that it provides you with I'm not saying that you cannot
do and you cannot connect for example your Microsoft Word with other chatbots
I'm not saying that you can do that easily but the point here is that the purpose
that co-pilot is used for is mostly it's a better compatibility when it
comes to other products of the same company which is Microsoft